<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Two Activities Challenge</string>
    <string name="activity2_name">Todays Passage</string>
    <string name="text_one">TEXT ONE</string>
    <string name="text_three">TEXT TWO</string>
    <string name="text_two">TEXT THREE</string>
    <string name="passage">TextView</string>
    <string name="passage_one">their identity or age. The missing registration is due to both social and economic factors. In sparsely populated areas, the authorities offices might be physically distant. But the distance to a mobile phone is often not very far in Pakistantoday - even in remote regions. For this reason, UNICEF ​​and Telenor made a pilot project in 2014. Together with the local authorities in the rural areas Punjab and Sindh, they developed an app for direct registration of births. Local staff, such as health workers, were equipped with the app, and within six months the proportion of registered births increased from 30 percent to 90 percent. The project is now being implemented all over Pakistan and the project is aiming for 700,000 registered births by the end of 2018. Another widespread issue in many parts of the world is the lack of a registered address. Three out of every four countries in the world do not have any efficient, systematic address register, and the UN estimates that</string>
    <string name="today_s_passage">Today\'s Passage</string>
    <string name="passage_two">of the night. Although the GPS is invented, the 16 digits are hard to remember, and there’s always the risk of typing in the number wrong. Together with two friends from the chess club at the prestigious private school Eton College in England, Sheldrick developed the app "what3words". The system divides the world into no less than 57 trillion squares of 3x3 metres each. Each square has a name consisting of three randomly chosen words. For example, the words with.harp.person will lead you to the White House in Washington DC and luring.ignoring.wipes to the Little Mermaid in Copenhagen. The system can of course be used by anyone, but especially for people without formal addresses in developing countries this has revolutionary potential. Any small cottage in rural areas or a shed in a slum now has its own "address" consisting of three words that anyone can remember, and everyone can find using the what3words app. According to the inventors, what3words is so far used by the post office in Mongolia, Djibouti, Tonga, Saint Martin and</string>
    <string name="passage_third">The conditions for employees in the clothing industry in Bangladesh are slowly improving due to, among other factors, strong-minded female factory workers who fight for better rights in the tough and ungrateful textile working industry.</string>
</resources>